http://www.theartnewspaper.com/information/privacy-policy

By using The Art Newspaper website you agree to our use of cookies as described in this Cookie Policy.Close noticeePaperNewsletterNewsArt marketMuseums & heritageBook ClubPodcastsDiaryVan Gogh blogMiami Art WeekCoronavirus resources NewsArt marketMuseums & heritageBook ClubPodcastsDiaryVan Gogh blogMiami Art WeekCoronavirus resources NewsArt marketMuseums & heritageBook ClubPodcastsDiaryVan Gogh blogMiami Art WeekCoronavirus resources NewsArt marketMuseums & heritageBook ClubPodcastsDiaryVan Gogh blogMiami Art WeekCoronavirus resources The Art Newspaper Privacy PolicyThe Art Newspaper® ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.This policy (together with the terms of use found here and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis upon which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting www.theartnewspaper.com, also known as theartnewspaper.com, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is U Allemandi & Co. Publishing Limited of 70 South Lambeth Road, London, United Kingdom, SW8 1RL. The company is registered in England under the company number 05166640.Information we collect from youHow The Art Newspaper processes the information it collects about you:Information you provide to us: This is information about you that you give us by filling in forms contained on our site www.theartnewspaper.com (the site) or by corresponding with us by telephone, e-mail or otherwise. It includes information you provide when you register to use the site, subscribe to our products, use our social media channels, enter a competition, promotion or survey and when you report a problem with the site. The information you provide to us may include your name, e-mail address and telephone number(s), financial and credit card information, company name, postal address andbilling address. Information we collect about you. With regard to each of your visits to our site we will automatically collect the following information:technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform,;information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL), clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time), materials you viewed or searched for' page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), methods used to browse away from the page, [and any phone number used to call our customer service number.Information we receive from other sources. This is information we receive about you if you use any other websites we operate or other services we provide or employ. We are working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies).CookiesOur website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our Cookie policy https://www.theartnewspaper.com/information/cookie-policyUses made of the informationWe use information held about you in the following ways:Information you give to us. We will use this information:to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services you request from us;to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about;to provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with information about goods or services we feel may interest you.If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please inform us about your preferences by sending an email with subject “OPT-OUT” to [subscribe@theartnewspaper.com] or call us at +44 (0)20 3416 9000to notify you about changes to our service;to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your device .Information we collect about you. We will use this information:to administer the site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;to improve the site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure;to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about goods or services that may interest you or them.Information we receive from other sources. We will combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We will use this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).Disclosure of your informationYou agree that we have the right to share your personal information with:Any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.Selected third parties including:business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with you;advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others. We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we will provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target. We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience;analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of the site;We will disclose your personal information to third parties:In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we will disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.If U Allemandi & Co. Publishing Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use contained at http://theartnewspaper.com/information/terms-and-conditions and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of U Allemandi & Co. Publishing Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.Where we store your personal dataAll information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers in the EU.Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where you were provided with a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.Your rightsYou have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by informing us about your preferences by sending an email with subject “OPT-OUT” to [subscribe@theartnewspaper.com] or by calling us at +44 (0)20 3416 9000.Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.
We recommend you check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.Access to informationThe Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request will be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.Changes to our privacy policyAny changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail, if you provide one. Please refer back to this page frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.ContactWe welcome your questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy. Please feel free to contact us by writing to The Art Newspaper at 17 Hanover Square, London, United Kingdom, W1S 1BNSubscribe to The Art Newspaper’s digital newsletter for your daily digest of essential news, views and analysis from the international art world delivered directly to your inbox.Sign upFind out how The Art Newspaper’s content platforms can help you reach an informed, influential body of collectors, cultural and creative professionals. For more information, contact info@theartnewspaper.com.SubscribeInternational networkInformationAboutContactAdvertiseCookie PolicyTerms and ConditionsPrivacy PolicySponsorship PolicyFollow usFacebookTwitterInstagramThe Art NewspaperCreated by wearegoatNewsletter signupOur daily newsletter contains a round-up of the stories published on our website, previews of exhibitions that are opening and more. On Fridays, we send our Editor’s picks of the top stories posted through the week. As a subscriber, you will also get live reports from leading art fairs and events, such as the Venice Biennale, plus special offers from The Art Newspaper.You may need to add the address newsletter@theartnewspaper.com to your safe list so it isn't automatically moved to your junk folder.You can remove yourself from the list at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe" link in the newsletter.CancelSubscribe to the list
